{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"6062/39",
			"answer":"6062/39",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5248/91",
			"answer":"5248/91",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5889/89",
			"answer":"5889/89",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1657/69",
			"answer":"1657/69",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8880/96",
			"answer":"8880/96",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"48.11/8.9",
			"answer":"48.11/8.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3703/8.4",
			"answer":"3703/8.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"427.7/0.44",
			"answer":"427.7/0.44",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.036/30",
			"answer":"3.036/30",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.095/0.11",
			"answer":"7.095/0.11",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}